Hey, hey, hey, hey, Miya, I got my bangs cut. How do you like it? Do you think it looks good?
How do you like it?
How do you like it? Idol
And now, as we come to the end of the show, Mr. Yuzuki...
Do you have any news?
Yes, well, first of all...
On Sunday, April 23rd, at Shinjuku Lenny's
We will be doing a one-ban live performance of Crown Pop on Sunday, April 23rd at Lenny's in Shinjuku.
Thank you very much.
The details are still under construction.
We hope you will have a chance to see the improved Crowne Pop.
We will do our best to give you a chance to see the improved Crown Pop.
Please come and see us for sure!
Thank you very much.
Also, from September to December this year, we will be going on a tour called "Hashtag Clap Cute Nationwide Spread Tour".
We're going to spread the "Clap Cute" throughout the country from Hokkaido to Okinawa, so please make sure you tag us with the hashtag "Clap Cute".
I'd be happy if you'd come to see me.
And we've got another important show coming up at the end of the year... on the 28th of December at zepp diversity.
And there is one more important live concert at the end of the year, on the 28th of December, Crown Pop will be performing at zepp diversity.
This is the live performance we did in 2021.
I'm going to show you the live performance that I did in 2021, where I was disappointed that I couldn't fill the venue with poppers, and I was also able to find more things that I regretted.
I'd like to do my best to show you a more improved club after two and a half years, so I'd be very happy if you could come and see us.
And I'm looking forward to seeing you there.
I'll definitely make you happy, so please look forward to it.
So it's revenge?
Yes, it's revenge!
The day before the revenge live, December 27th, is Yuzuki's birthday!
That's right, she will be 19 years old then!
We have to celebrate her birthday now.
Yes, I'd be happy if you could come and celebrate with us!
Plus, it would be great if you could come and celebrate with us!
I see... so that the concert will be a success, I'll give you a present from me.
I'm going to serve tea.
I'll give you a cup of tea.
I'd love to!
Today's tea is Saba-cha (mackerel tea) from Takatama Prefecture.
May I offer you a cup of tea?
Thank you very much.
I'll take it politely.
I'm a little nervous.
Please make it warm.
It's delicious.
After a proper talk about yourself like this.
After a proper talk about yourself like this, the tea soaks in.
It's nice.
You have the best Japanese language ability in the class.
Thank you, Yuki.
Thank you very much.
Excuse me... may I have one last, cute closing statement for the camera?
May I have a cute closing comment?
You're watching this.
Do you like Miya?
Do you want her to like you?
Wait a minute.
What? I didn't put it away, did I?
I'm sorry. It's just my usual language.
I'm sorry, that was the last thing you said.
I just wanted you to like me.
Thank you very much. I got it.
Thank you very much.
It's a miracle that I met you.
I want to fall in love with you.
Nighttime island idol
Thank you for watching!
This program was provided by So-san, Yushi-san, Nakayoshi no Mamono-san, Hakoushi Poppa-ji-san, and Hitsuji no Susu-san.
Hey, hey, do you like Miya? I love you, Miya.
Thank you very much for your contribution.